[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 54?",
      "correctAnswer": "2916",
      "options": [
        "2916",
        "2921",
        "2918",
        "2914"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 60?",
      "correctAnswer": "3600",
      "options": [
        "3605",
        "3602",
        "3598",
        "3600"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 34?",
      "correctAnswer": "1156",
      "options": [
        "1156",
        "1161",
        "1154",
        "1158"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 59?",
      "correctAnswer": "3481",
      "options": [
        "3481",
        "3486",
        "3483",
        "3479"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 30?",
      "correctAnswer": "900",
      "options": [
        "900",
        "902",
        "898",
        "905"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 16?",
      "correctAnswer": "256",
      "options": [
        "261",
        "256",
        "254",
        "258"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 27?",
      "correctAnswer": "729",
      "options": [
        "731",
        "727",
        "729",
        "734"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 21?",
      "correctAnswer": "441",
      "options": [
        "446",
        "443",
        "439",
        "441"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 63?",
      "correctAnswer": "3969",
      "options": [
        "3974",
        "3971",
        "3967",
        "3969"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 21?",
      "correctAnswer": "441",
      "options": [
        "443",
        "439",
        "441",
        "446"
      ]
    }
]